priceless.com 2016-06-16

# Privacy Notice

MasterCard International and its affiliates respect your Privacy.  Our Privacy Notice for Priceless Cities and Love This City has been updated and will be effective as of the Effective Date posted in this Privacy Notice. In general, we have recently updated many of our Site(s) to bring Priceless Cities and Love This City users a more enhanced experience. We have consolidated all of our various privacy notices into one global Privacy Notice to govern all Priceless Cities and Love This City Sites. A summary of the revisions are set forth below but we encourage you to read the entire Privacy Notice below.

1\. _Preamble_ _and How To Contact Us_ \- We have clarified the various MasterCard data controllers for Priceless Cities Sites operated in the EEA, Switzerland, Turkey, Russia and the rest of the world and added their contact information in the “How to Contact Us” section.

2\. _Personal Information You Provide Directly To Us_ – In general, we have clarified how we use the personal information that we use about you. 

3\. _Registration Process_ \- As our Priceless Cities Site(s) now allow for social media registration and integration, we have added more information on the data that we collect in connection with social media interactions. 

4\. _Social Media_ – Although you may “share”, “follow”, “tweet”, or “like” our content via social media networks, none of our Site(s) allow users to post to our Site(s) without our permission. We have clarified that we may contact you to seek your permission before using your social media posts and content on our Site(s).

5.  _Personalized Services and Recommendations_ – In addition to the personal data that you provide to us, we may also use information obtained about you from third parties or publically available information systems to deliver personalized services and recommendations that may be of interest to you.

6.  _Interest-Based Advertising_ \- In addition to the personal data that you provide to us, we may also use information obtained about you from third parties or publically available information systems to deliver advertising and offers that may be of interest to you.

7.  _Personal Data We Collect Automatically_ \- We have added a provision, _Information collection from mobile devices,_ which discusses our data collection when you interact with our Sites via a mobile device.

8.  _Your Rights and Choices_ – One some Sites, we may offer users choices to manage their cookie preferences through the Ghostery Cookie Consent Tool.

9.  _Information We Share_ \- We have clarified that we use commercial partners that provide redemption fulfillment services on our behalf and redemption of offers on commercial partner sites will be governed by their respective privacy policies.

10.  _Information We Share_ \- We have added a provision that discusses data collection and use through the Google mapping tool on mobile versions of our Sites.

Back to top

* * *

##  Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section: 

Back to top

* * *

##  Introduction 

MasterCard respects your privacy. In the context of the Love This City and Priceless Cities programs ( **“Priceless Cities”, “Love This City”** or **“Program(s)”** ), this Privacy Notice describes how we process personal data, the types of personal data we collect, for what purposes we use that personal data, with whom we share it, and the choices you can make about our use of the personal data. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the personal data and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.

MasterCard International Incorporated is the entity responsible for the processing of your personal data in the context of the Program(s) websites operated in North America, Latin America, Asia Pacific, Middle East and Africa found at [www.priceless.com](http://www.priceless.com/) or our related blog site, Love This City, operated at [www.lovethiscity.com](http://www.lovethiscity.com/) (the  **“Site(s)”** ).  

MasterCard Europe, MasterCard UK, and MasterCard France are the entities responsible for the processing of your personal data in the context of the Program(s) for our Sites operated in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, Russia and Turkey.

Your visit to the Site(s) and participation in the Program(s) is subject to this Privacy Notice, applicable [Terms of Use](https://www.priceless.com/en-us/terms-of-use.html) and to the [Cookies Notice](https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/4754?v=1) to the extent that you live in the European Economic Area, Switzerland or Canada.  Our privacy practices may vary among the countries in which we operate to reflect local practices and legal requirements.  This Privacy Notice applies to the personal data collected via Priceless Cities and Love This City only. It does not cover the collection and use of your personal data on any MasterCard branded websites or by your MasterCard Card issuers (e.g., your bank), or any other information or communications that may reference to MasterCard outside the Program(s) (e.g., communications from banks, card issuers). For more information about MasterCard’s privacy practices outside the scope of Priceless Cities or Love This City, please visit our Global Privacy Notice at [www.mastercard.com](http://www.mastercard.us/privacy/).

Children and minors (under the age of 18) are not eligible to use Priceless Cities.

Back to top

* * *

##  Personal Data We Collect And How We Use It 

We collect personal data in the context of Priceless Cities, Love This City or from other MasterCard programs and services. By personal data we mean “any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.” The personal data we process is either provided directly by you or collected automatically.  

Back to top

* * *

##  Personal Data You Provide To Us Directly 

The personal data you provide to us directly via the Program(s) are processed and used only for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. You are not required to provide personal data to access the Sites, but you may be required to provide us with personal data to participate in the Programs or for us to provide you with our services.  If you choose not to provide some data, this may affect the way you navigate on the Site(s) or the services that we can offer you. We may use the personal information we obtain about you to:

• Create and manage your profile account, provide the services, and to respond to your inquiries;

• Tailor content, recommendations, advertising and offers we display to you on the Sites and elsewhere online;

• Provide, administer and communicate with you about services, offers and promotions (including contests, sweepstakes, programs and other offers) and changes to our policies; 

• Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including by developing new products, offers and features; analyzing our offers; facilitating the functionality of our Sites);

• Assist us and third parties in the provision of offers to you via the Sites; 

• Monitor the use of and improve our interactive assets, including the Sites;

• Perform data analyses (including anonymization of personal information) to determine, among other measurements, business performance, number of registrants, channels and Site(s) performance;

• Enforce our [Terms of Use](https://www.priceless.com/en-us/terms-of-use.html) and other legal rights;

• Comply with applicable legal requirements and industry standards and our policies; 

• As may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency having or claiming jurisdiction over MasterCard or MasterCard's affiliate; and 

• Perform auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services.

Please find below information on how you may provide this data, the types of data you may submit, and how we may use the data:

_Registration Process:_ You may register to Priceless Cities through the Priceless Cities Site(s). In order to register and depending on your country that you register your account, we ask you to provide us with some of your personal data, such as your e-mail address, password, first and last name, date of birth, country of permanent residence and post code. You will also be asked to provide the first 8 digits of your MasterCard credit card through the registration process, offer redemption process or through your profile account. **** In addition, to complete your registration, you must accept the Priceless Cities Terms of Use, Privacy Notice and if applicable, the required Cookie Notice for the relevant Sites.  Your registration will be activated once you respond to the confirmation email that we will send you. 

Some Sites may allow you to login, register, access or otherwise connect to Priceless Cities via a social media network.  If you choose to login, register, access or otherwise connect to Priceless Cities, through a social media network such as Facebook, we may receive your first and last name, and email address (should you elect to provide your email information to us). In that case, your social media network will require you to agree that we receive your personal data **** from your social network provider in order to verify your credentials, populate your registration form and for future logins into your account. If you provide any personal data to us through a social media network, including through social media plugins located on Priceless Cities, and including by authorizing such social media network to provide information to us, then we may collect such information, and our use and disclosure of such information will be subject to this Privacy Notice. Note that we do not receive or store your social media password from these social media networks.

_Sign up Process for Communications:_ You may sign up on the Priceless Cities Sites to receive communications informing you about the Priceless opportunities via email, text or social media ( **“Communications”** ). In addition to signing up for Communications for Priceless, you may consent to receive information via email, text or social media about other MasterCard products and services including rewards, loyalty or privileges programs related products and services, opportunities or private events that become available. In order to send you Communications or information about Priceless Cities and/or MasterCard products and services, we use your personal data such as your name, e-mail address or mobile number, if applicable. You can, at any time and free of charge, choose not to receive any of those email Communications or through your profile account, by clicking on the unsubscribe link within the e-mail or by e-mailing us using this link: <https://www.mastercard.com/us/personal/en/general/email-opt-out.html>. For other methods of Communications (i.e. text or social media), we will advise you of ways to opt-out of those Communications at the time that you receive those Communications or by other means. We will not use your personal data for sending marketing Communications unless we have received your consent.     

_Your account:_   At any time after activating your registration and/or logging-in you can access your account on Priceless Cities by clicking on "My Account" where you can review or change your personal details (e.g., name, email address, country, password, etc.) or manage your e-mail subscriptions or preferences. __

_Social media:_  You may select to “share”, “follow”, “tweet” or "like" Priceless Cities or an offer via various social media providers. Social media networks are independent from MasterCard and any information collected by social media networks (such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, YouTube, etc.) in connection with Priceless Cities (including through social media plugins located on Priceless Cities) may be made public and subject to the applicable social media provider’s privacy policy, and not this Privacy Notice. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. For more information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how third party social media sites handle your personal data, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies and terms of use. MasterCard cannot be held liable for any of these social media networks’ content, use, or privacy practices.   

You may select to “share”, “follow”, “tweet” or "like" Love This City or an article that appears on Love This City via various social media providers, such posts will be governed by the __ applicable social media provider’s privacy policy, and not this Privacy Notice.  You may not post any content to any of our Sites without our permission.  From time to time, we may also feature certain social media posts (including user name and photos) on our Sites using the hashtag, #LoveThisCity or other related hashtags (“User Submissions”).  We will obtain the user’s consent prior to posting any User Submissions on our Sites and such User Submissions shall be subject to our Terms of Use. __

_Personalized Services and Recommendations:_  If you sign up for Communications, we may use your personal data to provide you with personalized services, offers and recommendations. We may also use other information obtained about you from companies that use or facilitate the use of other MasterCard products or services and from publicly available information systems to deliver personalized services, offers and recommendations that may be of interest to you.  For example, we may suggest products or other special marketing activities that may be of particular interest to you.  In order to provide you with personalized content and the most relevant offers, content or messages, we will gather the personal data that you have provided directly and the personal data that we have collected automatically in order to create a user profile.

_Other Features:_  We offer users of our Program various features for their information and enjoyment (e.g., sweepstakes, promotions, contests, blog), which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personal data so we can provide you with these features. For more information about how your data will be processed for these specific features, please refer to the relevant privacy notice, if any.

Back to top

* * *

##  Personal Data We Collect Automatically 

We may collect certain information by automated means (e.g., cookies, log-file, web beacons) when you visit the Sites. The data collected automatically are processed in order to improve the Program and to provide you with the best information and services. The information we collect in this way tells us, for example, how many users visited our website and the pages accessed, whether you have visited us before or if you are a new visitor, and helps us to identify features in which you may have the greatest interest. This information also allows us to make improvements and to enhance your experience.

_Log files and IP addresses:_  Log files are web server files (containing information such as the domain name or IP address, URL, the http response code, the website from where you visit us or the date and duration of your visit) that are automatically created when an Internet user visits a site. An IP address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit the Site(s), we may collect the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. For example, when you request a page from the Site(s), our servers log your IP address. In combination with other data, this information helps us to learn what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what types of offers our customers like to see. In addition, log files help us to detect disruptions to telecommunication equipment and to detect abuse of our telecommunication services.

_Information collection from mobile devices_ : If you access our Site(s), on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, we also may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address (e.g. MAC address), as well as information about your device’s operating system, mobile carrier, mobile Internet browsers, and other information described in this Privacy Notice.  In some regions, we may also have a Priceless Cities mobile application ( **“App”** ).  Note that the App has a separate privacy notice that will apply to the data collection and privacy practices and this Privacy Notice shall not apply to the App. 

_Cookies, web beacons and tracking links:_  We may use third-party web analytics services on our Site(s). The analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help us analyze how visitors use our Site(s). The information collected through these means (including IP address) is disclosed to these analytics providers, who use the information to evaluate use of our Site(s). We may offer users of our Site(s) choices to manage their preferences via our Cookie Consent Tool accessible via our AdChoices icon or via the Cookie Consent icon on our Sites.  Otherwise, you can opt out at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. To learn more about Cookies, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html> or our [Cookies Notice](https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/4754?v=1) available on the Site(s) in the European Economic Region, Turkey, Switzerland and Canada.

_Interest-Based Advertising:_ In some regions, we may collect information about your online activities on our Site(s) for use in providing you with advertising about materials and services tailored to your individual interests. We may also use your personal data and other information obtained about you from companies that use or facilitate the use of other MasterCard products or services and from publicly available information systems to deliver advertising and offers that may be of interest to you. You may see certain ads on other websites because we (and our partners) use data collected on our Site(s) to customize advertisements to you on third-party websites. This collection and use allows us to target our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based and contextual means. In connection with providing you customized advertisements, third parties on our websites may track your online activities over time and across third-party websites by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The information collected includes information about your visits to certain websites, the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on those websites. This data collection takes place both on our Site(s) and on third-party websites. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn about more about your ability to opt out of  interest-based advertising, click [here. ](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

Back to top

* * *

##  Your Rights And Choices 

You have the right to receive information about the data we store about you and to access your personal data by using the contact information provided in the “How To Contact Us” section below. You may also request at any time that your personal data be rectified, blocked or deleted if it is incorrect, inaccurate or outdated. Following any data request for access, rectification or deletion, we will accommodate your inquiry as required by applicable law. At any time, you may object on compelling legitimate grounds relating to your particular situation to the processing of your personal data by MasterCard, except when otherwise provided by the applicable law. We will not use any technical mechanism to subject you to a decision which produces legal effects and which is based solely on automated processing of data.

If you decide you no longer want MasterCard to process your personal data, at your request we will make information about you anonymous in the database, and any reference to you will be deleted.

You can, at any time and free of charge, choose not to receive any of those email Communications or information by clicking on the unsubscribe link within the e-mail or by e-mailing us using this this link: <https://www.mastercard.com/us/personal/en/general/email-opt-out.html> .  For other methods of Communications (text or social media), we will advise you of ways to opt-out of those Communications at the time that you receive those Communications or by other means. We will not use your personal data for sending marketing Communications unless we have received your consent.

On some Sites, we may offer  users of our site choices to manage their cookie preferences through the Cookie Consent tool displayed in the bottom right corner or accessible via the AdChoices icon. Your browser may tell you how to be notified and opt out of receiving certain types of cookies, including analytics and advertising cookies.

If we fall short of your expectations in processing your personal data or you wish to make a complaint about our privacy practices, please tell us because it gives us an opportunity to fix the problem. You may contact us using the contact details provided in the “How To Contact Us” section below. To assist us in responding to your request, please give full details of the issue. We will review and respond to all complaints within a reasonable time.

If you are located in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, you may direct us not to share your personal data with third parties, except (i) with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf, (ii) in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets, (iii) if disclosure is required by law or legal process, or (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraud or other illegal activity. If you are located in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, we use your personal data only for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Notice unless we have a legal basis, such as consent, to use it for other purposes. Where required by law, MasterCard obtains your prior opt-in consent at the time of collection for the processing of (i) personal data for marketing purposes and (ii) personal data deemed sensitive pursuant to applicable law.

If you are located in Latin America Countries (see Appendix 1), the procedure to exercise your personal data protection rights before MasterCard is the following:

In all cases, your request to exercise data protection rights must be made in writing and contain and/or enclose the following:

I. The name of the data owner and its domicile and/or other means to communicate to the same our response to the request received;

II. The documents needed to evidence the data owner’s identity or, when applicable its proxy’s identity and legal representation faculties;

III. The specific indication of the data protection right which you wish to exercise; and,

IV. A clear and precise description of the personal data for which the exercise of any data protection rights is pursued.

The validity of your request to exercise any data protection rights requires that the same meets all the requirements provided for it under the applicable legislation. In all cases the requestor shall accredit its status as owner of the personal data or alternatively its proxy condition with respect to the owner of the data as it may correspond.

MasterCard will communicate to you its decision within the term that is provided in the applicable law.

Back to top

* * *

##  Information We Share 

We do not disclose personal data collected in the context of the Program, except as described here.

We may share your personal data with our headquarters and affiliates, including MasterCard International Incorporated, MasterCard Europe sprl, MasterCard UK, and MasterCard France. We may also share your personal data provided with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf and in relation to the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. Examples include our operating platform providers, platform hosting providers, redemption fulfillment providers and customer service providers. When we use third party service providers, we take all necessary steps to ensure that our service providers maintain a high level of data protection. We require our service providers by contract to process the data in accordance with our instructions and to have safeguards in place designed to protect your personal data. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the data, except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.

When you redeem or purchase offers via Priceless Cities, you may be redirected to our commercial partner’s website where you will be asked to provide your personal data directly to the commercial partner and you will be governed by the privacy policy of their website. We may also share your personal data with our commercial partners in charge of redemption. These commercial partners will also process personal data for their own purposes under the terms of the agreement MasterCard has with each commercial partner in the context of the Program. For more information on each commercial partner’s privacy practices, we invite you to consult their respective privacy notice accessible on their redemption sites.  

If you are using the mapping tool available within the mobile web version of some Site(s), that mapping tool service is provided by Google. Their collection and use of any data through your interaction with their mapping tool is governed by Google’s privacy policy and terms of use, which we suggest you read. 

In addition, we may disclose personal data about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or pursuant to legal process, (ii) in response to a request from a court, law enforcement authorities or government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual criminal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any data we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation). Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will endeavor to use reasonable efforts to seek that the transferee uses the personal data you have provided through the Program in a manner consistent with this Privacy Notice. 

Back to top

* * *

##  Data Transfers 

We may transfer personal information to countries other than the country in which the data was originally collected.  These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information.  When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Notice.

MasterCard is a global business.  To offer our services, we may need to transfer your personal information among several countries, including the United States, where we are headquartered. We comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate safeguards for the transfer of personal information to countries outside of the European Economic Area or Switzerland.

Back to top

* * *

##  Links To Other Websites 

On the Site(s), we may provide links to other websites (including partner or third party sites) for your convenience. In particular, Priceless Cities offers you the possibility to share, link to or mention on social media outlets, such as Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest or Twitter, anything you may find of interest. These sites operate independently from the Program(s) and are not under our control. These sites may have their own privacy policies in place, which we strongly suggest you review when you visit them. We are not responsible for the content of these sites, any products or services that may be offered through these sites, the data processing activities that are conducted via those sites, or any other use of these sites.

Back to top

* * *

##  Records Retention 

MasterCard only retains personal data for as long as needed to fulfill the purposes for which they were collected, unless otherwise provided by law.

Back to top

* * *

##  Data Security 

We may hold your personal data in a variety of ways, including in electronic form.

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the personal data in our possession.

When you provide personal data online, we use the industry standard for encryption on the Internet – Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology – to help protect the information that you provide. This Internet encryption standard scrambles data as it travels from your device to our server. You will know that you are in a secure area of the Site(s) when a lock icon appears on your screen that the “http” prefix of our URL address changes to “https”. The “s” represents “secure”. We also use digital certificates to ensure that you are connected to the authentic Site(s).

Please note however that no collection or data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any data transmission.

We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (including unsolicited correspondence, such as letters, phone calls or e-mail messages). If you believe your user name and password have been compromised, please contact us by following the instructions provided in the section on “How To Contact Us” below. 

Back to top

* * *

##  Browser Do Not Track Signals 

Although the Site(s) currently do not have a mechanism to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals, we may offer users of our Site(s) choices to manage their preferences via our Cookie Consent Tool on our Sites and we will honor your preferences. To learn more about browser tracking signals and Do Not Track, please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

Back to top

* * *

##  Update To This Privacy Notice 

This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post a prominent notice on our Site(s) to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Notice and indicate at the top of the Privacy Notice when it was most recently updated.

Back to top

* * *

##  How To Contact Us 

If you are located in North America, the Asia Pacific, Middle East or Africa, the Caribbean, Central or South America, and (i) you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, or rectify, block or delete any personal data relating to you; (ii) you would like to obtain more information on how we process your personal data or access your personal data; (iii) you would like to withdraw your consent given for certain types of data processing; (iv) you would like to remove your e-mail address from our mailing lists; or (v) if you have any questions, comments, complaints or concerns about this Privacy Notice or our privacy practices, you may contact us by email at [privacyanddatausage@mastercard.com](mailto:privacyanddatausage@mastercard.com) or write to us at:

Global Privacy Officer  
MasterCard Worldwide  
2000 Purchase Street  
Purchase, New York 10552  
USA

If you are located in the United Kingdom, the entity responsible for the collection and use of your personal data in the context of the Program(s) available at [www.priceless.com/london](http://www.priceless.com/london) or [www.lovethiscity.com/eu/london](http://www.lovethiscity.com/eu/london) _ _ (or such other Site(s) that we may develop from time to time in connection to a city located in the United Kingdom) is MasterCard UK. If you would like to (i) obtain more information on how we process your personal data or to access your personal data; (ii) rectify, block or delete any personal data relating to you; (iii) withdraw your consent given for certain types of data processing; (iv) remove your e-mail address from our mailing lists; or (v) if you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us by [emailing us](mailto:london@priceless.com) at [london@priceless.com](mailto:london@priceless.com) or by addressing your mail to:

MasterCard UK  
Marketing Department  
10 Upper Bank Street  
Canary Wharf  
London E14 5NP  
UK

If you are located in France, the entity responsible for the collection and use of your personal data in the context of the Priceless Cities available at https://www.priceless.com/en/tourist/US/FR/paris/city.html ((or such other Site(s) that we may develop from time to time in connection to a city located in France) is MasterCard France. If you would like to (i) obtain more information on how we process your personal data or to access your personal data; (ii) rectify, block or delete any personal data relating to you; (iii) withdraw your consent given for certain types of data processing; (iv) remove your e-mail address from our mailing lists; or (v) if you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us by [emailing us](mailto:paris@priceless.com) at [paris@priceless.com](mailto:paris@priceless.com) or by addressing your mail to:

MasterCard France  
Service Marketing  
112 avenue Kleber  
75016 Paris  
France

With the exception of the United Kingdom and France, if you are located in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, Russia or Turkey, MasterCard Europe sprl may be the entity processing your personal information. If you would like to (i) obtain more information on how we process your personal data or to access your personal data; (ii) rectify, block or delete any personal data relating to you; (iii) withdraw your consent given for certain types of data processing; (iv) remove your e-mail address from our mailing lists; or (v) if you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us by email at [privacyanddatausage@mastercard.com](mailto:privacyanddatausage@mastercard.com) write to us at:

Global Privacy Officer  
MasterCard Europe sprl  
Chaussée de Tervuren 198A  
B-1410, Waterloo  
Belgium

To assist us in responding to your request, please give full details of the issue. We will review and respond to all complaints within a reasonable time. If you are not satisfied with how we respond, you may take your complaint to the applicable regulator in your jurisdiction.

For all other enquiries about your MasterCard card and your purchase, you must contact your Issuing Bank or the Participating Merchant. More information about how to contact them can be found on their respective websites.

Back to top
